Marvin Leath papers, Inclusive: 1954-1994, undated; Bulk: 1979-1991
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Legislative, 1978-1991, undated; 6
  - Leath Bills, 1979-1982; 2
    - 96th Congress, 1979-1980; 1
      - H.R. 3548, Bank Holding Company Application, 1979 (Box 358, Folder 24)
      - H.R. 3567, Soft Drink Interbrand Competition Act, 1979 (Box 358, Folder 25)
      - H.R. 3635, Disability Benefits Waiting Period, 1979 (Box 358, Folder 26)
      - H.R. 3674, Mandatory Minimum Prison Sentences for Dispensing Controlled Substances, 1979 (Box 358, Folder 27)
      - H.R. 3685, Registered Trademark Cancellation, 1979 (Box 358, Folder 28)
      - H.R. 3687, Use of Mirex on Fire Ants, 1979 (Box 359, Folder 1)
      - H.R. 3767, John Wayne Gold Medal, 1979 (Box 359, Folder 2)
      - H.R. 3892, Veterans Administration Healthcare, 1979 (Box 359, Folder 3)
      - H.R. 3989, Fort Mitchell Regional Veterans Cemetery, 1979 (Box 359, Folder 4)
      - H.R. 4015, Veteran Senior Citizen Healthcare Act of 1979 (Box 359, Folder 5)
      - H.R. 4237, National Grain Board, 1979 (Box 359, Folder 6)
      - H.R. 4282, Repeal Medicare Anti-Fraud Amendments, 1979 (Box 359, Folder 7)
      - H.R. 4484, National Energy Self-Sufficiency Act of 1979 (Box 359, Folder 8)
      - H.R. 4549, Motor Carrier Regulatory Improvement Act of 1979 (Box 359, Folder 9)
      - H.R. 4550, Joint Rates and Through Rates, 1979 (Box 359, Folder 10)
      - H.R. 4646, Capital Cost Recovery Act of 1979 (Box 359, Folder 11)
      - H.R. 4656, Free Association in Labor Organizations, 1979 (Box 359, Folder 12)
      - H.R. 4657, Student Freedom of Choice Act of 1979 (Box 359, Folder 13)
      - H.R. 4760, Alternative Fuels Engine Development Act of 1979 (Box 359, Folder 14)
      - H.R. 5127, Lamb Meat Quota Act of 1979 (Box 359, Folder 15)
      - H.R. 5225, Federal Firearms Law Reform Act of 1979 (Box 359, Folder 16)
      - H.R. 5228, Veterans Rehabilitation and Education Amendments of 1980, 1979 (Box 359, Folder 17)
      - H.R. 5499, Commission on Wartime Relocation & Internment of Civilians Act, 1979 (Box 359, Folder 18)
      - H.R. 5574, Farm Disaster Program Act of 1979 (Box 359, Folder 19)
      - H.R. 5602, Bread Labeling Act, 1979 (Box 359, Folder 20)
      - H.R. 5609, Basic Rights for Long-Term-Care Patients, 1979 (Box 359, Folder 21)
      - H.R. 5643, Rural Cooperative Business Income Act of 1979 (Box 359, Folder 22)
      - H.R. 5712, Commercial Boat Trips Through Grand Canyon, 1979 (Box 359, Folder 23)
      - H.R. 5813, Importation of Nonimmigrant Alien Students Involved in Violent Political Protest, 1979 (Box 359, Folder 24)
      - H.R. 5858, Sunset Review Act of 1979 (Box 359, Folder 25)
      - H.R. 6012, Tax Exemption for Social Security Title II Benefits, 1979 (Box 359, Folder 26)
      - H.R. 6206, Oil Exemption from Windfall Profit Tax, 1979 (Box 359, Folder 27)
      - H.R. 6223, Baltimore Public Facility Renaming, 1979 (Box 359, Folder 28)
      - H.R. 6260, Fusion Energy Research, Development, & Demonstration Act, 1979 (Box 359, Folder 29)
      - H.R. 6260 and 6308, Fusion Energy Research, Development, & Demonstration Act, 1980 (Box 360, Folder 1)
      - H.R. 6466, State Implementation Plans for Clean Air Act, 1980 (Box 360, Folder 2)
      - H.R. 6625, Removing Excessive Burdens on Coal Production, 1980 (Box 360, Folder 3)
      - H.R. 6725, Animal Damage Control Act of 1980 (Box 360, Folder 4)
      - H.R. 6759, Ban Importation of Foodstuffs with Harmful Pesticides, 1980 (Box 360, Folder 5)
      - H.R. 6906, Alcohol Farm Fuel Use Tax Act of 1980 (Box 360, Folder 6)
      - H.R. 7043, Repayment of Oil Import Fee, 1980 (Box 360, Folder 7)
      - H.R. 7102, Veterans Administration Health-Care Personnel Amendments of 1980 (Box 360, Folder 8)
      - H.R. 7211, Equitable Treatment of Royalty Owners, 1980 (Box 360, Folder 9)
      - H.R. 7362, Oil Taxes & Fees to Reduce National Debt, 1980 (Box 360, Folder 10)
      - H.R. 7394, Veterans Rehabilitation and Education Amendments of 1980 (Box 360, Folder 11)
      - H.R. 7414, “J. Marvin Jones Federal Building”, 1980 (Box 360, Folder 12)
      - H.R. 7441, National Defense Compensation Act of 1980 (Box 360, Folder 13)
      - H.R. 7506, Limitation on Government Recordkeeping Requirements & Actions Act of 1980 (Box 360, Folder 14)
      - H.R. 7824, Farm Labor Contractor Registration Act Amendments of 1980 (Box 360, Folder 15)
      - H.R. 8024, Change “Aubrey Lake’ to “Ray Roberts Lake”, 1980 (Box 360, Folder 16)
      - H.R. 8295, Amend Crude Oil Windfall Profits Tax Act, 1980 (Box 360, Folder 17)
    - 97th Congress, 1981-1982; 2
      - Bills Introduced by Leath, 1981-1982 (Box 360, Folder 18)
      - H.J. Res. 8, Term Limits for Supreme & Lower Court Judges, 1981 (Box 360, Folder 19)
      - H.R. 48, House Internal Security Committee, 1981 (Box 360, Folder 20)
      - H.R. 58, Congressional Review of Federal Programs and Tax Expenditures, 1981 (Box 360, Folder 21)
      - H.R. 65, Tax Exemption for Social Security Benefits, 1981 (Box 360, Folder 22)
      - H.J. Res. 84, “National Diabetes Week”, 1981 (Box 360, Folder 23)
      - H.J. Res. 102, “National Garden Week”, 1981 (Box 360, Folder 24)
      - H.J. Res. 109, “Gospel Music Month”, 1981 (Box 360, Folder 25)
      - H.R. 116, Civil Service Annuity Credit, 1981 (Box 360, Folder 26)
      - H.J. Res. 131, “Be Kind to Animals Week”, 1981 (Box 360, Folder 27)
      - H. Con. Res. 163, Peace Through Strength, 1981 (Box 360, Folder 28)
      - H. Con. Res. 178, Used Car Rule, 1981 (Box 360, Folder 29)
      - H.J. 220, Raoul Wallenberg, 1981 (Box 360, Folder 30)
      - H.J. Res. 267, Limit Number of Terms for Representatives & Senators, 1981 (Box 360, Folder 31)
      - H.R. 268, “Hungarian Freedom Fighter’s Day”, 1981 (Box 360, Folder 32)
      - H.R. 269, Workfare Program, 1981 (Box 360, Folder 33)
      - H.R. 316, Limitation on Government Recordkeeping Requirements and Actions Acts of 1981 (Box 360, Folder 34)
      - H.R. 317, Deportation of Nonimmigrant Alien Students Involved in Violent Political Protest, 1981 (Box 361, Folder 1)
      - H.R. 318, Windfall Profit Tax Exemptions, 1981 (Box 361, Folder 2)
      - H.R. 568, Estate & Gift Tax Changes, 1981 (Box 361, Folder 3)
      - H.R. 741, Eliminate Taxation of Fringe Benefits, 1981 (Box 361, Folder 4)
      - H.R. 1015, Prohibit Revenue Procedure 80-55, 1981 (Box 361, Folder 5)
      - H.R. 1053, Capital Recovery System, 1981 (Box 361, Folder 6)
      - H.R. 1064, Oil Exemption from Windfall Profit Tax, 1981 (Box 361, Folder 7)
      - H.R. 1100, Prisoner of War Benefits & Health-Care Services Act of 1981 (Box 361, Folder 8)
      - H.R. 1294, Uniform Margin Requirements, 1981 (Box 361, Folder 9)
      - H.R. 1339, Unified Credit Against Estate & Gift Taxes, 1981 (Box 361, Folder 10)
      - H.R. 1340, Maximum Reduction in Valuation Under Special Estate Tax Valuation, 1981 (Box 361, Folder 11)
      - H.R. 1400, Veterans Educational Assistance Act of 1981 (Box 361, Folder 12)
      - H.R. 1603, Stone, Sand, & Gravel Mining Operations, 1981 (Box 361, Folder 13)
      - H.R. 1765, Petroleum Displacement Act of 1981 (Box 361, Folder 14)
      - H.R. 1767, Food Stamp Act Reform Amendments of 1981 (Box 361, Folder 15)
      - H.R. 1776, Agency Rulemaking Improvements, 1981 (Box 361, Folder 16)
      - H.R. 1817, Steel Industry Compliance Extension Act of 1981 (Box 361, Folder 17)
      - H.R. 1911, Abolish the Legal Services Corporation, 1981 (Box 361, Folder 18)
      - H.R. 1956, Animal Damage Control Act of 1981 (Box 361, Folder 19)
      - H.R. 1969, Military Casualty Medical Treatment Planning Act of 1981 (Box 361, Folder 20)
      - H.R. 2036, Interest Payments on Overdue Sales to Federal Government, 1981 (Box 361, Folder 21)
      - H.R. 2038, Individual Housing Account Act, 1981 (Box 361, Folder 22)
      - H.R. 2039, Individual Housing Account Act, 1981 (Box 361, Folder 23)
      - H.R. 2136, National Cemeteries, 1981 (Box 361, Folder 24)
      - H.R. 2389, Safeguarding Taxpayer Rights, 1981 (Box 361, Folder 25)
      - H.R. 2410, National Cemeteries’ Construction Projects, 1981 (Box 361, Folder 26)
      - H.R. 2411, Memorial Plaques for Veterans’ Families, 1981 (Box 361, Folder 27)
      - H.R. 2451, Exemption from Crude Oil Windfall Profit Tax, 1981 (Box 361, Folder 28)
      - H.R. 2502, Extension of Duty-Free Status for Natural Graphite, 1981 (Box 361, Folder 29)
      - H.R. 2828, Underwriting State & Local Revenue Bonds, 1981 (Box 361, Folder 30)
      - H.R. 2888, Congressional Oversight of Veterans Administration Reorganization, 1981 (Box 361, Folder 31)
      - H.R. 3160, Prohibit Contractors from Working on Civilian Functions in Department of Defense, 1981 (Box 361, Folder 32)
      - H.R. 3300, Protect Firearm Owners’ Rights, 1981 (Box 361, Folder 33)
      - H.R. 3307, Minimum Number of Beds in Veterans Administration Medical Facilities, 1981 (Box 361, Folder 34)
      - H.R. 3363, Gross Income Exclusion, 1981 (Box 361, Folder 35)
      - H.R. 3364, National Mineral & Material Policy and Council, 1981 (Box 361, Folder 36)
      - H.R. 3499, Veterans Health Care, 1981 (Box 362, Folder 1)
      - H.R. 3502, Veterans Administration & Department of Defense Medical Facility Sharing, 1981 (Box 362, Folder 2)
      - H.R. 3520, Steelmaking Compliance Date Extension, 1981 (Box 362, Folder 3)
      - H.R. 3636, Farm Labor Contractor Act Amendment, 1981 (Box 362, Folder 4)
      - H.R. 3722, Federal Trade Commission Limitations, 1981 (Box 362, Folder 5)
      - H.R. 3918, Relief of Ursula Grubusch Oldham, 1981 (Box 362, Folder 6)
      - H.R. 3995, Disability Compensation Cost-of-Living Increase, 1981 (Box 362, Folder 7)
      - H.R. 4014, Food Safety Amendments of 1981 (Box 362, Folder 8)
      - H.R. 4354, Upper White Oak Bayou Flood Control Act of 1981 (Box 362, Folder 9)
      - H.R. 4786, Bankruptcy Improvements Act of 1981 (Box 362, Folder 10)
      - H.R. 4837, Army Cemetery Superintendents, 1981 (Box 362, Folder 11)
      - H.R. 4977, Naming Nuclear-Powered Aircraft Carrier, 1981 (Box 362, Folder 12)
  - Bills, 1979-1990; 3
    - 96th Congress, 1979-1980; 1
      - H.J.R. 39 Balanced Budget Amendment, 1979 (Box 362, Folder 13)
      - H.R. 96, Racial Discrimination Against Tax Exempt Status, 1979 (Box 362, Folder 14)
      - H.R. 160, Acreage Limitation Repeal Act, 1979 (Box 362, Folder 15)
      - H.J.R. 170, Congressional Term Limits Amendment, 1979 (Box 362, Folder 16)
      - H.R. 204, Taxpayer Bill of Rights Act, 1979 (Box 362, Folder 17)
      - H.J.R. 213, Balanced Budget Amendment, 1979 (Box 362, Folder 18)
      - H.J.R. 306, “National Defense Week”, 1979 (Box 362, Folder 19)
      - H.J.R. 320, “MacArthur Memorial Week”, 1979 (Box 362, Folder 20)
      - H.J.R. 409, Congressional Review of Agency Rules & Regulations, 1979 (Box 362, Folder 21)
      - H.R. 601, Uniform Procedure for Congressional Review of Agency Rules, 1979 (Box 362, Folder 22)
      - H.R. 1076 & 2727, Meat Import Act of 1979 (Box 362, Folder 23)
      - H.R. 1117, State Social Security Payments, 1978 (Box 362, Folder 24)
      - H.R. 1608, Veterans Health Care Amendments of 1979 (Box 362, Folder 25)
      - H.R. 1644, Medicare Coverage for Chiropractors, 1979 (Box 362, Folder 26)
      - H.R. 1650, National Digestive Diseases Prevention, Cure, & Control Act, 1979 (Box 362, Folder 27)
      - H.R. 1776, Administrative Rule Making Reform Act, 1979 (Box 362, Folder 28)
      - H.R. 2063, Regional Development Commission Act, 1979 (Box 362, Folder 29)
      - H.R. 2282, Veterans & Survivors Benefits Adjustment Act, 1979 (Box 362, Folder 30)
      - H.R. 2395, Belton Reservoir Conservation Storage Capacity, 1979 (Box 362, Folder 31)
      - H.R. 2744, Repeal Carryover Provision, 1979 (Box 363, Folder 1)
      - H.R. 3006, Public Debt Limit, 1979 (Box 363, Folder 2)
      - H.R. 3106, Taxation on Foreign Investment in U.S. Real Estate, 1979 (Box 363, Folder 3)
      - H.R. 3245, Independent Contractor Tax Status Clarification Act of 1979 (Box 363, Folder 4)
      - H.R. 3247, Crude Oil Transportation Amendments Act of 1979 (Box 363, Folder 5)
      - H.R. 3567, Soft Drink Interbrand Competition Act, 1979 (Box 363, Folder 6)
      - H.R. 3635, Disability Benefits Waiting Period, 1979 (Box 363, Folder 7)
      - H.R. 3674, Controlled Substances Sentencing Amendments, 1979 (Box 363, Folder 8)
      - H.R. 3685, Registered Trademark Cancellation, 1979 (Box 363, Folder 9)
      - H.R. 3892, Veterans Programs Extension & Improvement Act, 1979 (Box 363, Folder 10)
      - H.R. 3989, “Fort Mitchell Regional Veterans Cemetery”, 1979 (Box 363, Folder 11)
      - H.R. 4015, Veteran Senior Citizen Health Care Act, 1979 (Box 363, Folder 12)
      - H.R. 4282, Repeal Public Law 95-142, 1979 (Box 363, Folder 13)
      - H.R. 4484, National Energy Self-Sufficiency Act, 1979 (Box 363, Folder 14)
      - H.R. 4646, Capital Cost Recovery Act, 1979 (Box 363, Folder 15)
      - H.R. 4760, Alternate Fuels Engine Development Act, 1979 (Box 363, Folder 16)
      - H.R. 4970, Political Action Committee (PAC) Spending Limit Cuts, 1979 (Box 363, Folder 17)
      - H.R. 5127, Lamb Meat Quota Act, 1979 (Box 363, Folder 18)
      - H.R. 5225, Federal Firearms Law Reform Act, 1979 (Box 363, Folder 19)
      - H.R. 5288, Improve Veterans Educational Programs, 1979 (Box 363, Folder 20)
      - H.R. 5499, Executive Order #9066 Commission, 1979 (Box 363, Folder 21)
      - H.R. 5643, Rural Cooperative Business Income Act, 1979 (Box 364, Folder 1)
      - H.R. 5712, Limit Motorized Boats in the Grand Canyon, 1979 (Box 364, Folder 2)
      - H.R. 5858, Sunset Review Act, 1979 (Box 364, Folder 3)
      - H.R. 6012, Tax-Exempt Social Security Benefits, 1979 (Box 364, Folder 4)
      - H.R. 6223, Baltimore Public Facility Renaming, 1979 (Box 364, Folder 5)
      - H.R. 6260, Magnetic Fusion Program, 1980 (Box 364, Folder 6)
      - H.R. 6625, Coal Severance Tax Relief Bill, 1980 (Box 364, Folder 7)
      - H.R. 6725, Animal Damage Control Act, 1980 (Box 364, Folder 8)
      - H.R. 6759, Ban Importation of Foodstuffs with Harmful Pesticides, 1980 (Box 364, Folder 9)
      - H.R. 7043, Repayment of Oil Import Fee, 1980 (Box 364, Folder 10)
      - H.R. 7211, Equitable Treatment of Royalty Owners, 1980 (Box 364, Folder 11)
    - 97th Congress, 1981-1982; 2
      - Legislative Profile Book, 1981-1982 (Box 364, Folder 12)
      - H.J.R. 8, Term Limits for Supreme & Lower Court Judges, 1981 (Box 364, Folder 13)
      - H.R. 48, House Internal Security Committee, 1981 (Box 364, Folder 14)
      - H.R. 58, Sunset Review Act of 1981 (Box 364, Folder 15)
      - H.J.R. 65, Term Limits for Representatives & Senators, 1981 (Box 364, Folder 16)
      - H.R. 65, Tax-Exempt Social Security Benefits, 1981 (Box 364, Folder 17)
      - H. Con. Res. 82, Diminish Inequitable Capital Requirements, 1981 (Box 364, Folder 18)
      - H.J.R. 84, “National Diabetes Week”, 1981 (Box 364, Folder 19)
      - H.R. 116, Civil Service Annuity Re-computation, 1981 (Box 364, Folder 20)
      - H.J.R. 128, “National Beta Sigma Phi Week”, 1981 (Box 364, Folder 21)
      - H.J.R. 155, “Jewish Heritage Week”, 1981 (Box 364, Folder 22)
      - H. Con. Res. 178, Used Car Rule, 1981 (Box 364, Folder 23)
      - H.J.R. 202, “African Refugee Relief Day”, 1981 (Box 364, Folder 24)
      - H.J.R. 212, “National Cystic Fibrosis Week”, 1981 (Box 364, Folder 25)
      - H.J.R. 220, Raoul Wallenberg as Honorary U.S. Citizen, 1981 (Box 364, Folder 26)
      - H.J.R. 225, “Management Week in America”, 1981 (Box 364, Folder 27)
      - H.J.R. 267, Congressional Term Limits, 1981 (Box 364, Folder 28)
      - H.R. 269, Workfare Program, 1981 (Box 364, Folder 29)
      - H.R. 278, Funding Levels for Community Service Employment Programs, 1982 (Box 364, Folder 30)
      - H.R. 316, Limitation on Government Recordkeeping Requirements & Actions Act of 1981 (Box 364, Folder 31)
      - H.R. 317, Deportation of Nonimmigrant Alien Students Involved in Violent Political Protest, 1981 (Box 364, Folder 32)
      - H.R. 318, Child Care Agency Tax Amendments, 1981 (Box 364, Folder 33)
      - H.J.R. 346, “National Student Safety Week”, 1981 (Box 364, Folder 34)
      - H.J.R. 350, Federal Budget Procedures Constitutional Amendment, 1981 (Box 364, Folder 35)
      - H.J.R. 359, “National Disabled Veterans Week”, 1981 (Box 364, Folder 36)
      - H.R. 369, “International Franchise Day”, 1982 (Box 365, Folder 1)
      - H.J.R. 482, “National Non-Commissioned Officer (NCO)/ Petty Officer Week”, 1982 (Box 365, Folder 2)
      - H.J.R. 487, “Year of the Bible”, 1982 (Box 365, Folder 3)
      - H.J.R. 507, “National Recognition Day for the Registry of Interpreters for the Deaf”, 1982 (Box 365, Folder 4)
      - H.R. 568, Small Business & Family Farm Preservation Act, 1981 (Box 365, Folder 5)
      - H.R. 741, Eliminate Fringe Benefit Taxation, 1981 (Box 365, Folder 6)
      - H.R. 1015, Prohibit Revenue Procedure 80-55 Implementation, 1981 (Box 365, Folder 7)
      - H.R. 1053, Capital Cost Recovery Act, 1981 (Box 365, Folder 8)
      - H.R. 1064, Repeal Windfall Profit Tax on Royalty Oil, 1981 (Box 365, Folder 9)
      - H.R. 1100, Prisoner of War Benefits & Health-Care Services Act, 1981 (Box 365, Folder 10)
      - H.R. 1294, Uniform Margin Requirements, 1981 (Box 365, Folder 11)
      - H.R. 1313, Remove Excessive Burdens on Coal Production, 1981 (Box 365, Folder 12)
      - H.R. 1325, Repeal Davis-Bacon Act, 1981 (Box 365, Folder 13)
      - H.R. 1339, Unified Credit Against Estate& Gift Taxes, 1981 (Box 365, Folder 14)
      - H.R. 1340, Maximum Reduction in Valuation Under Special Estate Tax Valuation, 1981 (Box 365, Folder 15)
      - H.R. 1400, Veterans Educational Assistance Act, 1981 (Box 365, Folder 16)
      - H.R. 1603, Stone, Sand, & Gravel Mining Operations, 1981 (Box 365, Folder 17)
      - H.R. 1765, Petroleum Displacement Act, 1981 (Box 365, Folder 18)
      - H.R. 1767, Food Stamp Act Reform Amendments, 1981 (Box 365, Folder 19)
      - H.R. 1776, Administrative Rulemaking Reform Act, 1981 (Box 365, Folder 20)
      - H.R. 1817, Steel Industry Compliance Extension Act, 1981 (Box 365, Folder 21)
      - H.R. 1853, Ozone Layer Depletion, 1981 (Box 365, Folder 22)
      - H.R. 1911, Abolish the Legal Services Corporation, 1981 (Box 365, Folder 23)
      - H.R. 1956, Animal Damage Control Program, 1981 (Box 365, Folder 24)
      - H.R. 1969, Priority Medical Care for Injured Wartime Armed Forces Members, 1981 (Box 365, Folder 25)
      - H.R. 2038, Single Family Residential Unit Loans, 1981 (Box 365, Folder 26)
      - H.R. 2039, Veterans Health Care, Training, & Small Business Loan Act, 1981 (Box 365, Folder 27)
      - H.R. 2069, Penalty for Unlawful Assault on law Enforcement Personnel, 1981 (Box 365, Folder 28)
      - H.R. 2136, Construction & Acquisition of National Cemeteries, 1981 (Box 365, Folder 29)
      - H.R. 2301, National Right to Work Bill, 1981 (Box 365, Folder 30)
      - H.R. 2333, Federal Reserve Act Amendments, 1981 (Box 365, Folder 31)
      - H.R. 2389, Taxpayers Bill of Rights Act, 1981 (Box 365, Folder 32)
      - H.R. 2396, Federal Estate & Gift Taxes Elimination, 1981 (Box 365, Folder 33)
      - H.R. 2410, Roads to National Cemeteries, 1981 (Box 365, Folder 34)
      - H.R. 2411, Memorial Plaques for Veterans’ Families, 1981 (Box 366, Folder 35)
      - H.R. 2451, Exemption from Crude Oil Windfall Profit Tax, 1981 (Box 366, Folder 1)
      - H.R. 2502, Extension of Duty-Free Status for Natural Graphite, 1981 (Box 366, Folder 2)
      - H.R. 2828, Underwriting State & Local Revenue Bonds, 1981 (Box 366, Folder 3)
      - H.R. 2888, Congressional Oversight of Veterans Administration Reorganization, 1981 (Box 366, Folder 4)
      - H.R. 2889, Lamb Meat Quota Act, 1981 (Box 366, Folder 5)
      - H.R. 3160, Prohibit Contractors from Working on Civilian Functions in Department of Defense, 1981 (Box 366, Folder 6)
      - H.R. 3269, Malt Beverage Interbrand Competition Act, 1981 (Box 366, Folder 7)
      - H.R. 3300, Federal Firearms Law Reform Bill, 1981 (Box 366, Folder 8)
      - H.R. 3307, Minimum Number of Beds in Veterans Administration Medical Facilities, 1981 (Box 366, Folder 9)
      - H.R. 3363, Residential Housing Tax Incentives Act, 1981 (Box 366, Folder 10)
      - H.R. 3364, National Minerals Security Act, 1981 (Box 366, Folder 11)
      - H.R. 3423, Veterans Business Loan Act, 1981 (Box 366, Folder 12)
      - H.R. 3499, Veterans Health Care, Training, & Small Business Loan Act, 1981 (Box 366, Folder 13)
      - H.R. 3502, Veterans Administration & Department of Defense Medical Sharing Act, 1981 (Box 366, Folder 14)
      - H.R. 3520, Steel Industry Compliance Extension Act, 1981 (Box 366, Folder 15)
      - H.R. 3666, Repeal Titles XV & XVI of Public Health Service Act, 1981 (Box 366, Folder 16)
      - H.R. 3670, Grading & Labeling of Imported Meat, 1981 (Box 366, Folder 17)
      - H.R. 3704, Power Outage Contingency Plan, 1981 (Box 366, Folder 18)
      - H.R. 3962, Disposal of Dredge & Fill, 1981 (Box 367, Folder 1)
      - H.R. 3984, Farm Produce Storage Facilities, 1981 (Box 367, Folder 2)
      - H.R. 3995, Veterans Compensation Amendments Act, 1981 (Box 367, Folder 3)
      - H.R. 4033, Foreign Energy Investment Act, 1981 (Box 367, Folder 4)
      - H.R. 4554, Repeal Titles XV & XVI of Public Health Service Act, 1981 (Box 367, Folder 5)
      - H.R. 4709, Prompt Payment Act, 1981 (Box 367, Folder 6)
      - H.R. 4786, Bankruptcy Improvements Act, 1981 (Box 367, Folder 7)
      - H.R. 4837, Army Cemetery Superintendents, 1981 (Box 367, Folder 8)
      - H.R. 5432, Gold Medal to Admiral Hyman George Rickover, 1982 (Box 367, Folder 9)
      - H.R. 5705, Home Recording Act, 1982 (Box 367, Folder 10)
      - H.R. 5868, Replace Federal Income Tax System, 1982 (Box 367, Folder 11)
      - H.R. 6213, Independent Local Newspaper Excess Holdings Tax Exemption, 1982 (Box 367, Folder 12)
      - H.R. 6274, Farm Crisis Act, 1982 (Box 367, Folder 13)
      - H.R. 6286, Veterans Administration Nurse Shifts, 1982 (Box 367, Folder 14)
      - H.R. 6315, Better Care at Veterans Administration Medical Facilities, 1982 (Box 367, Folder 15)
      - H.R. 6348, Recognize the National Association of State Directors of Veterans Affairs, Incorporated, 1982 (Box 368, Folder 1)
      - H.R. 6350, Veterans Administration Health-Care Programs Improvement & Extension Act of 1982 (Box 368, Folder 2)
      - H.R. 6478, Employment Requirements for Food Stamp Program, 1982 (Box 368, Folder 3)
      - H.R. 6871, Residential Mortgage Investment Act, 1982 (Box 368, Folder 4)
      - H.R. 6782, Veterans Budget Reconciliation Act, 1982 (Box 368, Folder 5)
      - H.R. 6788, Employee Leave of Absence for Military Training, 1982 (Box 368, Folder 6)
      - H.R. 6794, Veterans Employment & Education Assistance Act, 1982 (Box 368, Folder 7)
      - H.R. 7014, Commission on Capital Markets, 1982 (Box 368, Folder 8)
      - H.R. 7402, Small Agricultural Cooperative Eligibility for Assistance, 1982 (Box 368, Folder 9)
    - 98th Congress, 1983-1984; 3
      - Legislative Profile Book, 1983-1984 (Box 368, Folder 10)
      - H.R. 10, National Development Investment Act, 1983 (Box 368, Folder 11)
      - H.R. 29, Recognize the Polish Legion of American Veterans, U.S.A., 1983 (Box 368, Folder 12)
      - H.J.R. 32, Congressional Term Limits, 1983 (Box 368, Folder 13)
      - H.J.R. 33, Congressional Term Limits, 1983 (Box 368, Folder 14)
      - H Con. Res. 43, Maintain Employment Positions in Senior Citizen Community Service Employment Programs, 1983 (Box 368, Folder 15)
      - H. Con. Res. 47, Administrator of Veterans Affairs as a Cabinet Member, 1983 (Box 368, Folder 16)
      - H.R. 58, Sunset Review Act, 1983 (Box 368, Folder 17)